謦灵风软影视论坛荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业用途
www.1000fr.net presents
你那手下叫什么?
So, your boy's name is what?
鼻涕虫
Snot.
- 你们叫他鼻涕虫? - 是的 鼻涕佬
- You called the guy Snot? - Snotboogie, yeah.
"鼻涕佬"
"Snotboogie."
他喜欢这名字?
He like the name?
- 什么? - 鼻涕佬
- What? - Snotboogie.
他老妈可是费尽心思给他想过正儿八经的名字
This kid whose mama went to the trouble of christening him Omar lsaiah Betts?
你瞧 他忘了自己的夹克...
You know, he forgets his jacket...
鼻涕开始乱流 不知哪个混蛋...
so his nose starts running, and some asshole...
没递包舒洁纸巾给他 反而叫他"鼻涕虫"
instead of giving him a Kleenex, he calls him "Snot."
所以 他永远是个"鼻涕虫"了
So, he's "Snot" forever.
似乎不公平
Doesn't seem fair.
我想 活着就是这样吧
Life just be that way, I guess.
那么谁开枪打了鼻涕虫?
So who shot Snot?
我才不要上法庭
I ain't going to no court.
狗娘养的也没必要爆了他的头啊
Motherfucker ain't have to put no cap in him though.
当然不必
Definitely not.
扁他一顿就好了 像我们一样
He could've just whipped his ass, like we always whip his ass.
- 我同意你 - 他杀了鼻涕虫
- I agree with you. - He gonna kill Snot.
认识他这么多年 他老干这种事
Snot been doing the same shit since I don't know how long.
怎么能因为这种破事就做掉一个人呢
Kill a man over some bullshit.
其实呢 每个星期五晚上...
I'm saying, every Friday night...
在胡同的折扣店后面 我们都会赌骰子
in the alley behind the cut- rate, we rolling bones, you know?
附近的混混都会来 大家赌到很晚
All the boys from around the way, we roll till late.
胡同里的小把戏 对吧?
Alley crap game, right?
每一次 鼻涕虫...他都会把钱卷跑
And like every time, Snot, he'd fade a few shooters.
玩上一阵子 等钱罐满了 抢了就跑
Play it out till the pot's deep. Then he'd snatch and run.
- 每次都是? - 小子管不住自己
- Every time? - Couldn't help hisself.
你看我这样理解对不对
Let me understand you.
每个周五晚上 你和你的哥们都会赌骰子 对吧?
Every Friday night, you and your boys would shoot crap, right?
同时 你的哥们鼻涕佬
And every Friday night, your pal Snotboogie...
他等到满地都是钱的时候 就会卷走跑路?
he'd wait till there was cash on the ground, then grab the money and run away?
- 你们让他那么做? - 我们会抓住他 然后痛扁他一顿
- You let him do that? - We catch him and beat his ass.
但也就这样而已
But ain't nobody ever go past that.
我得问问你
I gotta ask you.
如果每次鼻涕佬都会把钱卷走...
If every time Snotboogie would grab the money and run away...
为什么你们还让他来赌呢?
why'd you even let him in the game?
什么?
What?
如果鼻涕虫每次都偷钱 为什么你们还让他玩呢?
If Snotboogie always stole the money, why'd you let him play?
一定要啊 这里是美国 哥们
Got to. This America, man.
火线重案组 第一集 第一集 目标
The Wire S01E01 The Target
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* All the angels sing *
* About Jesus' mighty sword *
* And they'll shield you with their wings *
* And keep you close to the lord *
* Don't pay heed to temptation *
* For his hands are so cold *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
翻译&时间轴:VinE  校对:青色的花  Sync:VinE
"...多管闲事"  ---McNulty
- 猜猜他说了什么 - 说了什么?
- Guess what he says. - What?
"一定要啊 这里是美国"
"Gotta let him play, this America."
它妈的不是吧
No fucking way.
- 我干嘛瞎说 - 他供出开枪的人了吗?
- Would I make it up? - He give you the shooter?
三包Newport烟 一瓶Grape Nehi 他是大陪审团的人了
Three Newports and a Grape Nehi he's grand juried.
搞定了 Bunk
It's down, Bunk.
Barksdale是在12庭 对吧?
Barksdale's in Part 12, right?
西区的蓄意谋杀案
Project murder, Westside.
- 哪宗? - 算了
- Which one, now? - Never mind.
我要进去听一听
Gonna sit in on it for a bit.
你要去哪儿?
Where you gonna be?
我把这个给Nathan送去 然后回办公室
I'm gonna drop this off on Nathan, then I'm going to the office.
- 别接电话 Bunk - 好 好
- Don't answer no phones, Bunk. - Yeah, yeah.
照片册上的签名是你的吗?
And is that your signature on that photo array card?
是的
Yes.
这也是你在指认的照片上留下的名字缩写吗?
And those are your initials as well, next to the photo you identified?
是的
Yes.
Gant先生 今天的法庭上你看见
Mr. Gant, do you see the man you identified from that photo array card...
那位被指认的照片上的人了吗?
sitting in the courtroom today?
他就在那儿
He's right there.
请记录在案 证人指认出被告
For the record, the witness has identified the defendant...
D'Angelo Barksdale
D'Angelo Barksdale.
- 证人是您的了 - 谢谢
- Your witness. - Thank you.
就一个问题 Gran先生
Just one question, Mr. Gant.
在案发之前你有见过这位年轻人吗?
Have you ever seen this young man before the day in question?
没...没有
No.
没有其他问题了 法官大人
No further questions, your honor.
你可以退庭了 Grant先生
You're excused, Mr. Gant.
请传下个证人
Call your next witness.
法官大人 州院传证人Nakeisha Lyles
State calls Nakeisha Lyles, Your Honor.
你能否发誓 保证所述一切皆属实
Do you promise to tell the truth, the whole truth...
毫无虚假 不折不扣?
and nothing but the truth, so help you God?
我保证
I do.
夫人 请说出你的名字
Ma'am, can you state your name, please?
Nakeisha Lyles
Nakeisha Lyles.
- 你有工作吗? - 是的 我有
- And are you employed? - Yes, I am.
你的职务是什么 Lyles女士?
And what is your occupation, Ms. Lyles?
我是名保安
I'm a security guard.
在枪击案发生的5月4日 你是否正当班?
And were you employed as a security guard on May 4, the day of the shooting?
你那天的职责是什么?
What were your duties on that date?
去死吧 警探
我在221号治安亭里
I was in the booth of 221 .
就是Fremont大街 高楼大堂的治安亭里吗
And is that the guard booth in the lobby of the Fremont Avenue highrise?
是的
Yes.
你在防弹玻璃之后 是否对整个大堂有一个清晰的视野?
And you're behind bullet-proof glass, with a clear view of the lobby?
是的
Yeah.
很好
Good.
现在 Lyeles女士 我知道这对你来说有点困难...
Now, Ms. Lyles, I know this may be difficult for you...
但是你能告诉我你看到了什么吗?
but can you tell us what you saw?
一个男人 他正在等电梯...
A man, you know, he was waiting for the elevator...
此时 另一个男人开始殴打他...
and when another man just starts beating on him...
接着 一个被打倒在地...
and like, the one man, he got knocked down- -
- 受害人被打倒在地? - 不 是拿枪的人
- The victim got knocked down? - No, the man with the gun.
被打倒在地的男人有一把枪
The man who was knocked down had a gun.
你今天在法庭上有看到那个男人吗?
And do you see that man in the courtroom today?
没有
Nope.
抱歉?
Excuse me?
他不在这儿
He ain't here.
你不能...
You don't....
你做了口供
You testified.
Lyles女士 你还记得Barlow探员 给你看的这份照片册吗?
Ms. Lyles, do you remember when Detective Barlow showed you this photo array?
- 是的 - 很好
- Yeah. - Good.
我提醒你看一下这张被你署名的照片...
I call your attention to your initials which identify this photo...
是你指认枪杀Blanchard的人
as the man who shot Mr. Blanchard.
你有没有在照片上留下你的名字缩写?
Did you write your initials above that photograph?
他不是开枪的那一个
He ain't the one that did the shooting.
但是你指认了他
But you identified him.
那是因为他像那个开枪的人
That's 'cause he looked like the boy that did it.
瞧 这个开枪的人 我在一周后又看到他进了大厦
See, the one that did it, I saw him come in the building a week later.
你看到了另一个你认为是开枪的人?
You saw someone else you thought did the shooting?
没错 一星期之后
Right, a week later.
Lyles夫人 你在和探员的谈话中 你从未提及...
Ms. Lyles, when you spoke with the detectives, you never said anything about- -
我试过了 我打电话给警探...
I tried. I called Detective....
是的 打给Barlow警探 5月13日 两点
Yeah, Detective Barlow on May 13th at 2:00.
- 但是他没有回复我 - 干得好
- But he didn't call me back. - Nicely done.
- 你打电话给Barlow警探? - 是的 两次
- You called Detective Barlow? - Yeah, twice.
没错 我还把它写进了日志里
Yeah, I wrote it down in the log.
- 我要抗压梁木的报价 - 14美元
- I need a price for pressure- treated. - $14.
这个价格? 这是你打算给我开的价?
That's the price that you were going to quote me?
- 是的 - 你感觉到了吗 Mikey 有感觉吗?
- yes. - Do you feel that, Mikey, do you feel it?
因为我发誓 我的鸡巴正插进你的耳朵里
'Cause I swear to God that is my fucking dick in your ear.
- 很好 - 等一下 你这个不要脸的小偷
- That's nice. - Hang on, you fucking thief.
什么事?
What's up?
你最近去旁听过吗?
You been down the hall lately?
什么?
What?
你的案子刚才黄了 Barksdale的人翻案了
Your case just hit the wall. Barksdale's crew, they turned it.
两名目击证人 一份口供 它妈的没可能 哥们
Two eyewitnesses and a statement. No fucking way, pal.
你听我说 你这个臭小子 我不可能付这笔钱
You listen to me, you little shit, there is no way in hell I am paying that.
做梦
No.
你居然用我倒霉的车去带那臭婊子兜风
You use my goddamn car to chauffeur that dusty bitch around.
- 嘿 别发脾气 - 你不明白
- Yo, ease up. - You don't understand.
- 我处处为他 他却这样 - 上火没好处
- I did it for that man and he do this. - Getting heated ain't gonna help.
- Greggs 你的人说什么? - 管她说什么
- Greggs, what's your bird saying? - It ain't what she says.
是吗? 那你说什么?
Yeah? What do you say?
我说等着 猪头
I say we wait, shithead.
就是他
That's him.
好了 冷静 姑娘
All right, easy, girl.
- 嘿 Herc 听到了没? - 是的 我们看到了
- Yo, Herc, you got that? - Yeah, we see.
- 警员待命了吗? - 他们待命中
- Are the uniforms on the horn? - They're on hold.
- 那是Ghost - 好的 很好 Tiff
- That's Ghost. - All right, good, Tiff.
告诉我会看到什么 姑娘
Now tell me what I'm seeing, girl.
- 他会找到小Mike - 然后呢?
- He gonna get little Mike. - Then what?
Mike拿着钱回来
Mike come back with the money.
等他们放货 车进入小区里再拦下
Wait on the drop, take the car when it's deep in the block.
我不想来场追捕
I don't want no foot chase.
收到
Copy.
盯上了
Got it.
上 上 上 司机是我的
Go, go, go. The driver's mine.
右边那栋
Get the house on the left.
趴倒地上 趴下!
Get down. Get on the ground.
- 把手放脑袋后面 - 把手举起来
- Put your hands behind your head. - Get your hands up.
- 关掉引擎 - 在街角抓住那个狗娘养的
- Shut the engine. - Get that motherfucker around the corner.
把钥匙递出来 把钥匙扔到车外
Hand the keys out. Drop the keys out of the car.
马上扔出来 下车
Drop them now. Get out of the car.
趴倒这里来 马上
Get down right here, right here.
趴下
Get down.
乘客 把你的手伸出车窗
Passenger, put your hands out of the car window.
两只手都伸出车窗 用你的右手打开车门
Both hands out of the car window. Use your right hand, open up the car door.
慢点 走出车来
Slowly. Step out of the car.
走出车子
Step out of the car.
趴到地上
Down on the ground.
趴在地上
好了 好了 让他蹲牢子去
That's it, take his ass to jail.
- 你看住他了 Carv? - 我看住他了
- You got him, Carv? - I got him.
- 看看这玩意 - 双腿交叉
- Look at this shit. - Cross your legs.
看这个
Look at this.
你看到他干了什么吗 你看到他干了什么吗
You see what he did? Do you see what he did?
为什么他要把枪扔我车顶上 它妈的非刮了漆不可
Why he throw the gun on my car? Shit gonna scratch the paint.
- 留在车里 - 让他离我车远点
- Stay in the car. - Tell him to leave my car be.
- 它妈的留在车里 - 他凭什么那么做
- Stay in the fucking car. - That shit just ain't right.
你拿这玩意儿要干什么?
Whatcha doing with something like that?
你手里拿了什么?
What you got here?
你该看看这臭娘们看我的眼神 Kima
You should've seen the way this bitch was looking at me, Kima.
这小丑吓得差点屁滚尿流
Ugly little fucker almost shit his pants he was so scared.
对吧?
Right?
两把枪 记得吗?
Two guns, remember?
两把?
Two?
没出事儿 Kima 别紧张
It's all good, Kima, ease up.
全体起立
All rise.
Baltimore市第12巡回法庭现在开庭
Part 12 of the Circuit Court of Baltimore City is now in session.
请就座
Be seated.
首席陪审员 你们有一致裁决了吗?
Madame Forelady, you have a unanimous verdict?
对于指控被告D'Angelo Barksdale
As to the defendant D'Angelo Barksdale...
一级谋杀罪 你们有何认定?
how say you to the charge of murder in the first degree?
无罪
Not guilty.
对于二级谋杀罪的指控 你们有何认定?
How say you to the charge of murder in the second degree?
无罪
Not guilty.
太好了
Yeah.
- 我说什么来着 - 请就座
- That's what I'm talking about. - Be seated.
- 是你 老爹 没错 - 秩序!
It's you, daddy, yeah, that's right.
- 起码你让他们忙活了一阵 - 请就座
- At least you made them work for it. - Be seated.
感谢陪审团审理此案
The jury is to be thanked for its services in this case.
庭警将被告送回审前羁押所
Deputies will return defendant Barksdale to pretrial...
办理释放手续
for processing prior to his release.
你以为我会放心上?
Think I give a fuck?
总有一天我会送你进去
I'll be chalking you off one night.
- 祝你过得愉快 - 嘿 Stringer 走了
- You have a nice day. - Yo, Stringer, let's go.
探员?
Detective?
探员
Detective.
法官要求见你
Judge asked to speak with you.
- 那里是怎么回事 - 我们输了
- What the hell happened out there? - We lost.
你跟的案子?
Were you on this?
- 这件? - 是的
- The case? - Yeah.
不 是Barlow的案子 McLarney协助过而已
No, it was Barlow, with an assist from McLarney.
如果是Barlow的案子 你到庭干什么?
If it was Barlow's case, why are you in court?
没理由
No reason.
你喜欢旁听不是自己办的谋杀案?
You just like coming to court on murders you don't even work?
让你兴奋吗?
Just for the thrill of it?
当你和客人打成一片时...
When you start coming with the customers...
离关门大吉之日就不远了
it's time to get out of the business.
你是个法官 不该出言不逊
You shouldn't talk dirty now that you're a judge.
既然我是个法官 我说什么都可以
Now that I'm a judge, I can say anything I damn please.
那个叫Barksdale的小子 是Avon Barksdale的外甥
That Barksdale kid, he's a cousin to Avon Barksdale.
谁?
Who?
Avon Barksdale和Stringer Bell
Avon Barksdale, Stringer Bell.
在Franklin Terrace(高层公寓区) 兴风作浪了一年
The crew that's been running Franklin Terrace for a year.
Stringer Bell?
那个在法庭里拿着黄色便笺簿 戴着眼镜...
That was him in court with the legal pad and the glasses...
让每个证人闻风丧胆的家伙
scaring the living shit out of every witness.
他和其余成员 Wee-Bey...Savino...Stinkum
Him and the rest of his crew, Wee- Bey, Savino, Stinkum.
我看见他们了
I saw them.
你想过清理法庭吗?
You think about clearing the court?
凭什么? 这是个自由国度的开放法庭
On what basis? It's an open court in a free nation of laws.
这里可是Baltimore啊
I thought it was Baltimore.
Barksdale在Terrace 掌管着七栋大楼里的五栋
Barksdale has five out of seven towers in the Terrace.
那就是10处楼梯井 全天供应麻醉剂和白粉
That's 10 stairwells in five high- rises, going 24/7 for dope and coke.
而那不过是在高楼里
And that's just the towers.
还有平房 街角 也都是他的
The low- rises, the avenue corners, they're all his, too.
你怎么知道的?
How do you know this?
- 大家都知道 - "大家"是指谁?
- Everybody knows it. - Define "everybody".
西区每个人
Everybody on the Westside.
Barksdale和Bell 他们是新势力
Barksdale and Bell, they're the new power.
我是说 这几个月里 他们已经搞出了10具或者12具尸体
I mean, they've dropped 10 or 12 bodies in as many months.
三宗案子都翻案了 跟在你庭上发生的一样
Beat three cases in court doing the same thing they just did.
- 谁在查他们? - 局里?
- Who's working on them? - In the department?
说真的 没人
Nobody, really.
最近我们都在忙着整治街道
We're a little busy doing street rips, you know.
社区警务之类的
Community policing and all that.
那么 既然不是你的案子 你干嘛关心?
So, if it's not your case, why do you care?
谁说我关心了?
Who said I did?
再来一次 再来一次
One more time.
Barltimore警察局
缉毒科
别再玩了...
Stop playing....
该死的
Fuck me.
你有证物组的递交号码了吗?
You got submission numbers for the ECU?
- 没有 - 去要啊
- Nope. - Get them.
为什么是我?
Why me?
你想抓人 就要做提交
You want the collar, do the submissions.
- 你让我打头阵? - 轮到你了
- You giving me the start? - It's your turn.
证物组的分机是多少?
What's the extension for ECU?
我像是你的跟班吗?
Do I look like your bitch?
- 我们要没收奔驰吗? - 不 我答应过我的姑娘了
- We taking the Mercedes? - No, I promised my girl.
车是在她名下
Car's in her name.
缉毒科
Narcotics.
副队 二号线
Lieutenant. Line 2.
给你
Here you go.
- 该死的 我不会打字 - 谁它妈会啊
- Fuck me, I cannot type. - Who the fuck can?
千禧年都过了...
Millennium been and gone...
史密斯和歌罗娜打字机:美国上世纪40年代著名打字机
我们它妈的还在和Smith-Corona打交道
and we still fucking around with Smith- Corona.
我们得搞些计算机来
We need to get them computers hooked up.
他们一年之前就答应来培训我们
They promised to train us a year ago.
像你这种白痴 就算有计算机 有什么用?
What would an ass- ignorant motherfucker like you do with a computer?
我不知道 买卖股票之类的
I don't know, trade stocks and shit.
你是说打飞机吧
Jerk off, you mean.
要是我们搞来了计算机 Herc肯定会沉迷于那些色情玩意...
We get them computers hooked up, Herc'll be deep into some porn...
Kima肯定还是在那台老古董上浪费时间
and Kima'll still be bangin' out her 24s on that old piece of shit.
- 得去楼上一次 - 什么事?
- Gotta go upstairs. - What's up?
副局在大发雷霆
Deputy's throwing some kinda piss-fit.
警长知道了吗?
Major know?
他现在就在上面
He's up there now.
估计一嘴巴"尿"(气得脏话连篇)
With a mouthful of piss, probably.
难道我们的警长还不知道那是什么味道吗?
Like our major don't know what that tastes like?
这就是上下级 宝贝 屎球总是从上面滚下来
It's the chain- of- command, baby, the shit always rolls downhill.
狗娘养的 我们在说尿
Motherfucker, we talking about piss.
尿也是 好好想想
Piss does too, think about it.
- 屎是滚的 尿是流的 - 都是由上而下
- Shit rolls, piss trickles. - Downhill, though.
你怎么能肯定
You don't know that for sure- -
- 你有看到过... - 不是想转移你们两个帅哥的话题...
Not to change the subject on you two charmers...
但是为什么只有两个物证组的号码
but why are there only two ECU numbers?
- 毒品和枪支 - 两把枪 对吧?
- Dope and guns. - Two guns, right?
那就是三样了
That's three.
去它的 Kima
Fuck it, Kima.
你想做得好 就自己干吧
You want a job done right, you gotta do it your own self.
他的意思是只要一上街
He means that we are an effective deterrent...
我们就是打击毒品犯罪的尖兵
on the war on drugs when we are on the street.
- 整死那些操蛋的 对吧? - 没错
- Fucking motherfuckers up, right? - Indeed.
谁鸟这些报告
Fuck the paperwork.
- 收尸 爆头 - 五马分尸
- Collect bodies, split heads. - Split them wide.
- 扬西区的范儿 - 没错
- The Western District way. - All right.
你们这两个狗屁英雄主义真是恶死我了
You heroic motherfuckers kill me.
和毒品的战争...
Fighting the war on drugs...
每次只能开一次杀戒
one brutality case at a time.
小妞 你怎么能把这狗屁叫战争
Girl, you can't even call this shit a war.
为什么不能?
Why not?
战争会结束
Wars end.
你要那它写下来吗?
You gonna write that down?
我看到自己的呼机上 显示你的号码有多开心啊
How happy am I to see my pager go off with your call number?
缴到这种烟就抽抽...
Smoke 'em if you got 'em...
因为这垃圾的烟草真是不赖
because this motherfucker is as ripe as they get.
- 我们又没当班 是Nolan那队 - 我知道 我知道
- We aren't up, Nolan's squad is up. - I know.
但是你接了那该死的电话 对吧?
But you had to answer the fucking phone.
- 我有信用卡要还 - 不戒了它 你别想还清
- Got to pay down my credit cards. - Not off him, you ain't.
狗娘养的 我只离开了你一分钟 看你做了什么
I leave you alone for a minute, what do you do?
- 行了 你说的我听到了 - 那你复述一遍啊 Bunk
- All right, I heard you. - Say the words, Bunk.
- 得了 伙计 - 说啊
- Come on, man. - Speak to me.
那你打算扔下Bunk不管了? 这可不对 Jimmy
So, you gonna cut and run on the Bunk? That shit ain't right, Jimmy.
好吧 那这就是我一个人的案子了 我的报告
All right, then, this is my case. My file.
如果到头来发现是宗谋杀案...
This shit comes back a murder...
你就会袖手旁观 站在一边笑话我
you ain't gotta do shit but stand there and laugh at me.
你开心了 你这个婊子
You happy now, you bitch?
这教会了你狗拿耗子多管闲事的下场
This'll teach you to give a fuck when it ain't your turn.
可能这根本不是谋杀
It ain't even gonna be a murder.
这个傻蛋也许只是进来嗑药 结果磕过头了
This motherfucker probably came in here to take a shit and just fell out.
我打赌没什么花头
I bet there ain't nothing to it.
- 你去希望吧 - 你去哪儿?
- You hope. - Where you going?
回办公室 我该属于的地方
Back to the office, where I belong.
你这个发烂的臭鬼
You moldering motherfucker.
别想搞出个谋杀来
Don't even think about coming back a murder.
想都别想
Don't even think of that shit.
明天之前 副队 别让我失望
By tomorrow, Lieutenant. Don't fail me.
- 警长生气了 - 他该生气
- Major's pissed. - He should be.
他甚至回答不了副局的提问
He didn't have answers for the deputy's questions.
什么问题?
About what?
Avon Barksdale
Avon Barksdale.
谁?
Who?
我也不知道啊
That's what I said.
Avon Barksdale它妈的是谁?
Who the fuck is Avon Barksdale?
跟据正直可敬的Phelan法官大人...
According to the right honorable Judge Phelan...
他是一个频频牵涉偶发凶杀案的西区混混
a Westside player who apparently indulges in the occasional murder.
在今天之前我从没听说过Barksdale先生
Now, as of today, I never heard of Mr. Barksdale...
但在明天之前...
but by tomorrow....
好吧 我们知道什么呢?
All right, what do we know?
跟据法官的说法 他控制着西区的高楼地盘
According to the judge, he has the Westside high- rises.
大多是在Terrace
The Terrace, mostly.
听上去相当棘手
Sounds like a bunch of bullshit to me.
也许是的
Maybe so.
一定得今晚?
It's gotta be tonight?
警长想在早上看到文件
Major wants it filed by morning.
打电话给药管局的Andrews 看看他们手上有没有这个家伙的资料
Call Andrews at DEA. See what they have on this mope.
那凶案科呢? 如果这个家伙是个杀人犯..
What about Homicide? lf the guy's doing murders- -
凶案科的警长也列席了会议
Homicide major was in the same meeting.
他的人肯定也会抓耳挠腮凑资料的
His people will be scrambling to get something on paper, too.
我怀疑他们是否愿意和你分享 但是你可以试试
I doubt they'll be willing to share, but you can try.
Barksdale...Avon
Barksdale, Avon.
有出生日期吗?
Got a DOB?
Barltimore警察局
凶案科
Jay
Jay.
你它妈的一整天晃哪儿了?
Where the fuck you been all day?
喝酒 抽烟
Drinking, crack smoking.
在Baltimore的街头给自己找恩客
Whoring myself on the streets of Baltimore.
好吧 只要你有理由
Okay. Just so you have an excuse.
但是你那倒霉的搭档接了个报案电话
But your fuck of a partner picked up the phone, caught a call.
- 是的 我在那儿看到他了 - 是吗 他有什么发现
- Yeah, I saw him out there. - Yeah, what'd he get?
一间无人公寓里的腐尸
Decomp in a vacant apartment.
操
Fuck.
Nolan小队当值 该是他们的案子
Nolan's squad was up, that one should be theirs.
一具腐尸 也许查下来是自然死亡
It's a decomp. Maybe it comes back a natural death.
- 你这么想? - 在Poe Homes 想得美
- You think? - In the Poe Homes, no fucking way.
等一下
Hold up.
在你闪之前 警长想找你谈谈
Major wants to talk to you before you roll out.
谈什么?
What about?
妈的 我怎么知道 我只是你的警督
Fuck should I know, I'm only your sergeant.
它妈的坐下 探员
Sit the fuck down, Detective.
出什么事了?
Something wrong?
把你的屁股挪到椅子上
Put your ass in the chair.
你看到这两个了吗 McNulty 你看到它们了吗?
You see these, McNulty, you see them?
这些是给你的
These are for you.
它们会伴随着你直到我们两清
These are for you for as long as it takes me to get even.
警长 怎么...
Major, what- -
别喊我警长 你这个背后使诈 自以为是的烂货
Don't "Major" me, you backstabbing, smartass piece of shit.
你去法院它妈的到底是要干什么?
What the fuck you doing over at the courthouse anyway?
它妈的你跟个狗屁法官说个屁?
Why the fuck are you talking to some shitbag judge?
这是送给你的 McNulty
These are for you, McNulty.
这边的这根会狠狠地插进 你它妈的爱尔兰小屁眼里
This one over here is going up your narrow fucking lrish ass.
而这边的这根坏家伙 会插进你它妈的狗眼里
And this bad boy over here is in your fucking eye.
我跑到上面去回答关于某个 从未听说过的黑佬的问题...
I'm upstairs answering questions about some project nigger I never heard of...
一个传说中从我们组10件凶案中脱身的家伙
who's supposedly beat my unit out of 10 murders.
三件
Three.
他们只在庭上赢了三次
They only beat three in court.
副局问我的时候是10件
I got the deputy asking about 10.
是的 他们犯了10件 我们只起诉了其中三起
No, they did 10, we only charged them with three.
你满嘴喷屎
You're full of shit.
长官 你可以自己看文件
Sir, you can check the files.
Maurice Scroggins Toreen Boyd...Roland Leggett
Maurice Scroggins, Toreen Boyd, Roland Leggett.
那个在Saratoga的楼梯井里发现的女孩
The girl they found in the stairwell in Saratoga...
叫Collette还是什么
Collette something or other.
我是说 警长 这些家伙真的存在
I mean, Major, these guys are real.
他们在Gerard Bogue的案子里打败了我 就像对Barlow做的一样
They beat me up on the Gerard Bogue case just like they did Barlow.
Scroggins?
我没有Scroggin凶案的记录
I don't have an H- file on Scroggins.
他那是去年夏天死的
He was last year, summer.
脑袋后面中了两枪 在平房院子里
Two in the back of the head, low- rise courtyard.
让我搞清楚一些事
Let me understand something.
你在用一件去年的案子 让副局给我脸色看?
You are having the deputy bust my balls over a prior- year case?
我是要你给我干这种事吗 你这个不听话的小混蛋?
Is this what I need from you, you insubordinate little fuck?
警长 瞧 我真的很对不起
Major, look, I'm really sorry.
Phelan 他和我 我们之前打过交道
Phelan, he and l, we go back a little, you know?
他想知道我对他庭上那帮人的了解
He wanted to know what I know about the crew in his court.
- 我没想越权上报.... - 我不得不一无所知地上楼...
I had to go upstairs knowing nothing...
向副局解释 他为什么被人询问那些凶杀案
and explain to the deputy why he's getting calls about murders...
那些没人在乎的死案
that don't mean a shit to anybody.
瞧 长官 是这个法官耍了我
Look, sir, this judge, he fucks me up.
他问我问题 我回答了
He asks me a question and I answer it.
我不知道他会给谁打电话
I didn't know he was gonna call anybody.
你最近可别犯什么错 探员
You have my attention, Detective.
你最好万事小心
My complete, undivided attention.
- 是的 长官 - 你去哪儿?
- Yes, sir. - Where you going?
- 我的班是8点到4点 - 不
- I'm 8:00- to- 4:00. - No.
- 你给我打字去 - 什么长官?
- You're typing. - Sir?
副局要求在八点准时看到桌上的报告
Deputy wants a report on his desk at 0800.
报告?
A report?
干净 没有错字
Clean, no typos.
弄得规范点 署上我的名字
Make it look right, then put my name on it.
你需要我提到所有的谋杀案 还是低调处理?
Do you want to reference all the murders? Or should I soft- pedal that?
纸早就包不住火了 不是吗?
Fucking horse is out the barn door, right?
别再让我看上去像个傻瓜
Let's try not to make me look stupid twice.
在你罗列案子的时候 给我每段前面加个点
And when you list the cases, put a little dot next to each one.
- 副局喜欢圆点 - 对不起 警长 真的
- Deputy likes dots. - I'm sorry, Major, really.
这里的黑佬真是疯了
Niggers crazy in there, yo.
东区 西区 人人都在抱怨
Eastside, Westside, everybody beefing.
- 你没问题的吧 是吗? - 当然没 我们在这儿根基深着呢
- You ain't got no problem, right? - Hell no, we deep in there.
你们在法院的道也深呢
Y'all deep down at the courthouse, too.
坐在那里 我真不知道它妈的会发生什么事
Sitting there, I didn't know what the fuck would happen.
我在想...
I'm wondering...
你们要怎么帮我呢 知道么
how y'all gonna make it happen for me, you know?
不过你们对女保安的那一手真是太漂亮了
Slick what y'all did with that security lady though.
太绝了
That shit was tight, yo.
我们走走
Let's walk.
规矩是什么?
What's the rule?
我知道规矩
I know the rule.
说出来
Say it.
别在车里谈事
Don't talk in the car.
或是电话里 或者任何不是我们的地盘
Or on the phone or in any place that ain't ours.
不要对任何不是我们的人开口 但那是你
Don't say shit to anybody who ain't us. But it was just you.
是你它妈的车
It's your fucking truck.
别在车里说事
Don't talk in the car.
Marcel是怎么回事?
What about Marcel?
不 我没邀请Marcel
No, I ain't inviting Marcel.
你想让他滚?
You want him out?
我不在乎你做什么
I really don't give a shit what you do.
说真的 不
Actually, no.
下去 让那个混蛋付他的酒钱
Go down there and make that motherfucker pay for his drinks.
这个扫把星
The bum.
- 你好吗? - 你好吗 Dee 很高兴见到你
- How you doing? - What's up, Dee, good to see you.
你好吗 伙计
What up, man?
嘿 你还记得那次 想让小Kevin栽在Gerard身上的警察吗
Yo, you remember the cop that tried to pin Gerard on little Kevin?
哪个?
Which one?
白人警探 黑头发
White detective, black hair.
到处打探消息的家伙
The one that was knocking on all the doors.
他怎么了?
What about him?
他今天到庭旁听了
He showed up in court to watch.
放了什么话?
Word?
你为什么跟那个狗娘养的说话?
What are you talking to that motherfucker for?
该死的 Dee
Damn, Dee.
他说了什么吗?
He say anything?
不 只是坐在后面
No, just sat in the back.
- 嘿 你好吗 伙计 - 你怎么样
- Yo, what up, money? - What you got?
来 我有东西给你
Come on, I got something for you.
你一定感觉不错
You must feel good.
你知道是怎么回事
You know how that go.
你说什么?
Say what?
我是说 监狱可不是玩笑
I'm saying, you know, jail ain't no joke.
我可不知道什么监狱
I don't know shit about jail.
我也不打算知道 你懂吗
I don't plan on knowing shit about jail, you feel me?
如果你想谈论监狱 你可以坐到Marcel旁边去
You wanna talk about jail though, you can go sit down next to Marcel.
- 他刚回来 - 对 你说得没错
- He just got home. - True, you right.
坐下
Sit your ass down.
我知道事情闹得不好看
I know it ain't go so good.
但是那个黑佬 Pooh 他偷袭我
But that nigger, Pooh, he caught me off guard.
- 他疯子似的攻击我 - 所以你开枪杀了那个混蛋?
- He came at me like he was crazy. - So you shoot the motherfucker?
我是说 死的不是他就是我
I'm saying, it was him or me.
你在我们自己的楼里
You in our building.
两边楼上都有你的人
You got people on both stairs.
院子里还有更多的人
You got more motherfucking people out in the court.
而且你还有把枪
And you got a gun.
所以 我想弄明白的是...
So, what I'm trying to figure out is...
你它妈的你最后怎么会搞到 开枪打了这个黑佬....
how the fuck you end up shooting this nigger...
在安全亭前 当着所有人的面?
in front of the security booth with all them people?
我是说 这个黑佬冲着我来...
I'm saying, this nigger was coming at me...
- 就是他想要做了我 - 这不关他的事
- Iike he was trying to end me. - This ain't about him.
我要说的是你
It's about you.
你没法让那个家伙离开大堂
You can't play him out of that lobby.
你也打不过他
You can't take a beating neither.
所以你首先做的 就是冲动行事...
So, the first thing you do, you get all emotional...
你拿出了自己的枪 做了愚不可及的事
you pull your gun out, you do some dumb shit...
于是我们不得不一通忙活
that now we got to work around.
我知道
I know.
你说的它妈的没一句是我想听的
You ain't said one motherfucking thing I want to hear.
你说得没错 我是说 我得多动动脑子
You right. I mean, I gotta start thinking more.
你一直都这么说 你是对的
You be saying that all the time and you right.
但是我是说 我的意思是...
But I'm saying though, I mean...
你们对女保安的那一手
the shit y'all pulled with that security lady.
太绝了 我是说 那个检察官
It was tight. I mean, that state lawyer.
我从没见过一个白人女人脸变得那么红
I ain't never seen a white woman turn so red.
你该到场的
You should've been there.
嘿 伙计 你是家人 明白吗?
Yo, man, you family, okay?
但是这种事情很破财
But that shit cost money.
费时又破财
It cost time and money.
你会补偿吗?
You gonna make that right?
一定 你会看到的
Most def, you gonna see.
等我回到大楼 我会让手下好好干
When I get back to the tower, I'm gonna push them niggers.
好吧
All right.
过来
Come here.
别这副样子走出去
Don't walk out of here like that.
- 你是家人 好吧 - 好的
- You family, all right? - All right.
- 你瞧 爱不会变 - 嗯
- You know it's always love. - Yeah.
打得轻点
Type quieter.
你不必等在这儿 亲爱的
You didn't have to wait up, love.
你的受害人是不是心脏病?
Your boy have a heart attack?
不 我那么暗示了..
No, I went that way...
但是看到这个之后 Frazier医生没有买账
but Doc Frazier didn't bite when this popped up.
你死定了
You seriously fucked.
说到完蛋 你怎么还在这儿?
Speaking of fucked, why are you here?
我做了件坏事 Bunk 但不是我的错
I did bad, Bunk. It wasn't my fault.
真的
Really.
Phelan法官在陪审团放走 Barksdale那小子的时候 叫住了我
Judge Phelan pulled me up when the jury let the Barksdale kid go.
他毕竟是个法官 我有什么说什么
Him being a judge and all, I let go of some shit.
他来叫板了?
He raise a stink?
警长被行政副局逮住了 明早之前我得完成一份报告
Major got busted by the Deputy Ops and I gotta have a report by morning.
就像你说的 狗拿耗子多管闲事吧
There you go, giving a fuck when it ain't your turn to give a fuck.
看看他们 Cole
Look at them, Cole.
跟这两个高尚无私的公仆共处一室
Don't it make your dick bust concrete to be in the same room...
没有让你的老二自惭形秽?
with two noble, selfless public servants?
我知道 我很骄傲
I know I'm proud.
告诉我你结了这一件
Tell me you put this one down.
当然没有
Of course not.
当然你这儿的这位搭档 不得不去法庭
Of course your partner here has to go over to the courthouse...
把我们的工作向法官汇报
and lay our business out in front of a judge.
那么你听说了?
So, you heard?
警长打到我家里 说我该早点起来...
Major calls me at home, says I should get in early...
看你的稿子
read over your shoulder.
上面有圆点
It's got dots.
副局喜欢圆点
Deputy loves dots.
去你和你的点
Fuck you and your dots.
我不过是回答了那家伙的问题 他可是个不折不扣的法官
All I did was answer the guy's questions. He's a fucking judge.
而副局是不折不扣的副局长
And the Deputy's the fucking Deputy.
是他 不是法官...
And he, not the judge...
对你狗屁前途有着生杀大权
has what's left of your beshitted career in his hot little hands.
只要他开个口...
He says so...
你明天就得去西区巡街
you're walking foot in the Western tomorrow.
去它妈的 我就是从西区来的
Fuck it, I came from Western.
你还有什么地方不想去的 混球?
Where don't you want to go, asshole?
物证科? 人事部?
Evidence Control? Personnel?
总部安全部?
Headquarter Security?
船上
The boat.
水警组?
The marine unit?
是的 那些柴油让我晕船
Yeah, those diesel fumes, they make me feel seasick.
很好 继续努力
That's good, keep it up.
我赌10块 你会开船值夜班
I'll go this against $10, you're riding the boat, midnight shift.
听听他的 Jimmy
Listen to the man, Jimmy.
嘿 Stringer
Yo, Stringer.
你来早了
You here early.
是的 今天我要上阵了
Yeah, I'm on my game today.
Eggy弄新货上架了吗?
Eggy put out testers?
Dee
Dee.
今天生意有变
New deal today.
你被外派了 去管Pit那的买卖
You going out on point, picking up business in the Pit.
什么?
What?
你被派到平房区去了
You the man in the low- rises.
平房? 你不是让Ronnie Mo管的Pit吗
The low- rises? You got Ronnie Mo in the Pit.
Ronnie Mo今早调去了851大楼
Ronnie Mo got 851 this morning.
我从夏天开始就管理高楼了 为什么现在要把我派去平房区?
Why you gonna put me in the low- rises when I had a tower since summer?
是的 你经营过大楼
Yeah, you had a tower.
如果你脑子能长记性 那么还有可能再次让你管理大楼
And you might have a tower again if you can keep your mind to shit.
它妈的什么意思!
This is fucked up.
如果你让我们看到你也能管理Pit的生意 那你很快就会回到城里来
You show us you can run the Pit, and you'll be back uptown soon enough.
我舅舅知道吗?
My uncle know about this?
你觉得呢?
What do you think?
- 嘿 Bey - 嘿
- Yo, Bey. - Yo.
送小表弟一程
Give little cousin here a ride down the way.
- 派你的人去跟着Daniels - 好的
- Have your people deal with Daniels. - Right.
你会派你手下McNulty吗?
You gonna send your man McNulty?
跟他讲讲上下级的道理
Tell him about chain- of- command.
你自己去说吧 他对我来说是个死人
Tell him yourself, he's dead to me.
嘿 你在找Ronnie吗 他进城了
Yo, you looking for Ronnie Mo, he uptown.
我知道
I know.
你是Dee吧?
You Dee, right?
你不是管大楼的吗?
Wasn't you in the towers?
是的
Yeah.
那为什么把你派到这儿来? 你数错钱了还是什么?
Why they put you down here, yo? You mess with the count or something?
我杀了个黑佬
I killed a nigger.
进来
Yeah.
警长?
Major?
算上从药管局那得到的资料 我们对这家伙了解多少?
Counting what we got from the DEA, how much do we have on this guy?
- 长官 - 副队 手头上 我拿了几页纸?
Lieutenant, in my hand, I'm holding how many pages?
- 四页 长官 - Rawls它妈的拿了本"电话簿"
- Four, sir. - Rawls had a fucking phone book.
我能说什么 他们有10起没破的凶杀案
What can I tell you, they got 10 open murder files.
如果我们也有他的10件案子 那我们手上不会只有一本厚厚的报告
If we had 10 shots at him, we'd have more than a fat file.
我在楼上也是这么说的
I said that upstairs.
他们没法靠谋杀案抓住这家伙
They can't put this guy down for a murder...
- 所以打算叫我们来做他们的活儿 - 不是打算 是已经拉上我们了
- so they're getting us to do their work. - Not getting us, they got us.
实际上 他们找上了你
They got you, in fact.
什么 先生
Excuse me, sir?
Dawson有York和Cator的案子 所以只剩下你
Dawson has the York and Cator case, that leaves you.
该死的 和凶案科碰个头...
Shit. Look, set something up with Homicide...
随便叫上你的哪个手下
and whoever else you want from your squads.
- 检察官呢? - 嗯 我们也该叫上他们
- State's Attorney? - Yeah, we should call them, too.
该死的屎盆子
Fucking shitstorm.
副队 三号线
Lieutenant, line 3.
行政副局
Deputy Ops.
好了
Here we go.
给我合上
Close that for me.
咖啡有什么用?
What's the coffee do?
给钱一点质感 不让它看上去那么白
Give it that money feel, so it don't seem so white.
对
Yeah.
至少 你这次正反面都印了
Leastways, you got it on both sides this time.
是的
Yeah.
好了 把真的给我
All right, give me the real.
等等 我们拿真钱干什么
Wait, why are we gonna use real money?
我们可不是在和Lemon街的傻子打交道
We're not burning no lemon street chumps here.
懂吗?
Feel me?
我会了
I'm down.
你会了 Johnny会了
You down? Johnny's down.
买卖来了 能给我份1比1吗?(可卡因和海洛因混装出卖)
You got that gig. Can I get a one-on-one?
嘿 Poot
Yo, Poot.
嘿 Wallace
Yo, Wallace.
这就是Ronnie Mo定的流程?
This the way Ronnie Mo set it up?
- 是的 - 伙计 这怎么行
- Yeah. - Man, this is fucked up.
瞧 你们不能在拿了顾客钱后 马上把东西给他们
Look, you can't serve your customers straight up after taking they money.
要是有人拍照 那就被逮个正着了
Somebody snapping pictures, they got the whole damn thing.
明白我说的吗?
See what I'm saying?
你拿到了钱...
You get paid...
让他们到外面溜达去
you send they ass off around the building, yo.
然后你在给货 明白吗?
Then you serve. All right?
我们得更严格 别再图省事
We gotta start tightening up, man. No more shortcuts.
你有多少了?
What's your count?
270了
I'm up $270.
你得数数
You want to count it.
我是说 我不知道你在大楼里是怎么做的
I mean, I don't know how you do shit up in the towers.
- 但是在这儿 你得数数 - 该死的
- But down here, you want to count it. - Shit.
你们这群人被骗了
Y'all niggers been burnt.
这就是你要说的?
That's what you got to say?
它们看上去像钱吗 狗娘养的?
This look like money, motherfucker?
钱是绿的 钱摸上去像钱
Money be green. Money feel like money.
- 这玩意儿在你眼里是绿的吗? - 这上面它妈的有个死人总统
- That shit look green to you? - It got a dead fucking president on it.
我才不管什么狗屁总统
I don't give a fuck about the president.
- 这玩意儿它妈的不是钱 - 他不是总统
- That shit ain't money. - He ain't no president.
- 你什么意思? - Hamilton(Hamilton是美国第一任财政部长)
- What you mean? - Hamilton.
- 他不是总统 - 哥们 你疯掉了?
- He ain't no president. - Nigger, is you crazy?
它妈的不是美国总统
Ain't no ugly- ass white man get his face on no legal...
这张丑脸怎么可能印上去
motherfucking tender except he president.
这要是还有下次 你就别收钱了 听到了没?
This shit happen again, you off the money. You hear me?
你就别再干了
You ain't even gonna be serving no more.
给我滚到Vine街头
Your ass be out on the bottom end of Vine street...
40:40液盎司一瓶的便宜麦啤的通称  50:条子
喝酒 望风 听到了没
sucking on a 40, yelling "5-0". You hear me?
它妈的给我滚
Get the fuck out of here.
就这样?
That it?
你有意见?
No.
你得控制速度 伙计
You need to pace that shit, man.
Johnny 哥们 你听到我说的吗?
Johnny, man, you hear me?
我没事
I'm cool.
不 哥们 你会晕过去的...
No, man, you gonna fall out...
像你最近几次这么个注射法
slamming that shit like that one of these days, boy.
嘿 哥们 我想带你入门...
Yo, man, I'm trying to give you a little game, man...
但是你总想自作聪明
but you want to pretend like you know something.
我知道很多 Bubbs
I know a lot, Bubbs.
不 你是个菜鸟
No, you green.
我要让你变成老手
I'm trying to get you brown, man...
但你还是太嫩
but you still green.
你要让我变成老手
You gonna make me brown?
嘿 Bubbs?
Yo, Bubbs?
明天让我去骗
Let me do the scam tomorrow.
拜托 伙计 我准备好了
Come on, man, I'm ready.
嘿 我已经是老手了
Yo, I'm brown.
该死 哥们 你连一半水准都没有
Shit, man, you ain't even fucking beige.
行政副局长 Ervin H. Burrell办公室
- 钓鱼执法 - 是 长官
- Buy- busts. - Yes, sir.
不要搞长期盯梢 不要偷拍 不要搞电话录音
No long surveillances, no Kel recorders, no DNRs.
我要尽可能地速战速决
I want to get in and out as quickly as possible.
有道理
That makes sense.
Phelan不只是个法官 他还是个搞政治的
Phelan isn't just a judge, he's a political entity.
如果他有什么要求 我会满足他
If he asks for something, I want to give it to him.
为什么他会问起这个Barksdale
Why is he asking about this Barksdale?
这个星期他看到他的检察官在庭上被打败了
He watched his state's attorney get beat up in his court this week.
- 输了起凶杀案 - 我们一直在输案子
- Lost a murder case. - We lose cases all the time.
但是法官碰巧追问起了这一件
But a judge happens to be asking about this one.
- 你要用谁? - 带头探员?
- Who you using? - Lead detective?
- Greggs 她是我目前最得力的人 - 我认识她吗?
- Greggs, she's my best right now. - I know her?
做了4个月的刑侦科 从东区的缉毒组过来的
CID for four months. Came over from Eastern DEU.
- 那凶案科派谁来? - 那就是Rawls警长的决定了
- Who's Homicide sending? - That's up to Major Rawls.
如果是派McNulty来跟你 我是不会惊讶的
I wouldn't be surprised if you get McNulty.
- 你认识McNulty吗? - 不算认识
- You know McNulty? - Not really.
就是他在法官面前大嘴巴的
He's the one who mouthed off to the judge in the first place.
- 他跟法官打报告? - 是的 那是我的理解
- He talked to the judge? - Yeah, that's my understanding.
所以 如果他来这里 长个心眼
So, if he comes over on this, watch your back.
你需要什么 对我开口
You need anything, you ask me.
我会全力帮你
I'll give you all the help I can.
- 但是别给我惊喜 - 明白 长官
- But no surprises. - Yes, sir.
随时向我报告
Keep me briefed.
美国联邦调查局
Baltimore辖区办公室
- 嗨 我是McNulty 市凶案科的 - 有谁在等你吗?
- Hi, McNulty, City Homicide. - Is anyone expecting you?
是的 5队的特别探员Fitzhugh
Yeah, Special Agent Fitzhugh, Squad 5.
他在等我 我能...
He's expecting me, can l- -
得有人来接你
Not without an escort.
好吧
All right.
请Fitzhugh探员到前台来
Agent Fitzhugh to the front.
- Fitz - 兄弟
- Fitz. - Brother.
- 她能认出坏蛋 - 不是针对个人的 Jimmy
- She can spot a bad one. - Nothing personal, Jimmy.
你知道现在他们是怎么搞安保的
You know how they are with security nowadays.
我知道他们怎么对待本地人
I know how they are with locals, yeah.
那么 什么事 探员?
So, what's up, g-man?
- 好东西 伙计 好东西 - 是吗?
- Good stuff. - Yeah?
你们的人给了我们一件大案子
Your man gave us a hell of a case.
说到线人 Jimmy 你可真会挑人
Comes to informants, Jimmy, you can pick 'em.
他是我迄今为止合作过的最棒的线人
He's one of the better Cl's I've ever worked.
你在搞窃听?
You up on a wire?
不止这样
That and more.
你瞧 他的语气像是在说 他手上有笔破天荒的大买卖
So, like, he be talking like he got some type of record deal, you know?
- 哥们 拜托 - 那个家伙...
- Man, please. - That nigger.
- 那个妞吃定你了 - 老天爷
- The pussy has you. - Jesus Christ.
- 棒极了 不是吗? - 你是怎么录到这个的?
- Pretty fucking great, huh? - How'd you get this on tape?
那不是录像 是现场直播 兄弟
That's not tape. That's live, brother.
直播?
That's live?
直播 就在Homer大道三层的无电梯公寓里
Live from a three- story walkup on Homer Avenue...
Pimlico的贫民窟
in the bottoms of Pimlico.
这是正在发生的事?
This is going on right now?
- 就在我们说话的这会儿 - 怎么弄的?
- As we speak. - How?
光纤透镜
Fiber- optic lensing.
摄像头就在墙后的一个洞里
Camera's behind a hole in the drywall.
小得看上去就像一个钉上去的钉子
So small it looks like a nail might've made it.
麦克风在哪儿? 这玩意听上去真清楚
Where's the mic? These motherfuckers sound great.
两个遥控装置按在护壁隔热层后面
Two remotes behind the baseboard heating ducts.
今天桌上有价值3000的原料
That's about $3,000 of raw on the table today.
我们从纽约一直跟到这里
We followed it all the way from New York.
你去纽约是查这个?
You're up in New York on this?
算是碰碰看
We could be.
我们在那里查到了多米尼加人
We're backing into some Dominicans up there.
如果想 我们可以马上靠 Title III(有线窃听法)抓了他们
We could have a Title Ill on them right now if we wanted.
打错了仗 哥们
Wrong war, brother.
大多数小队都派去反恐了
Most of the squad's been transferred to counterterrorism.
这是我们最后一起没了的毒案了
This thing's the last drug case we got pending...
而我得在月底前结案
and I gotta shut it down by the end of the month.
- 你们不再缉毒了? - 是的 暂时
- You guys are getting out of drugs? - Yeah, for a while.
我们没有人手来跟大案子了
We just don't have the manpower to stay on anything big.
从大楼倒了之后(指911双子塔倒塌)
Not since those towers fell.
怎么 我们没有足够的热情 来同时加入两场战争吗?
What, we don't have enough love in our hearts for two wars?
- 我们真丢脸 对吧 - 我猜是的
- Joke's on us, huh? - I guess so.
不过 你牵出了一件大案子 哥们
Still and all, you give great case, brother.
我希望你能跟我们一起干
I wish you could've worked it with us.
就是这个 20美元 收好了
That's it, here's $20, hook it up.
2加2
Two and two.
- 等下 - 什么
- Hold up. - What?
- 2加2 - 拜托 伙计 我没时间搞这个
- Just two and two. - Come on, man, I ain't got time for this.
- 我给了你20美元 伙计 - 你给了我20?
- I gave you $20, man. - You gave me $20?
1加3
One and a short three.
- 那得找你 2... - 7块
- So you get, two- - - $7.
- 等等 - 找我7块 快点 伙计
- Hold up. - I get $7 back. Come on, man.
冷静点
Calm down.
等等 等等 你把我搞糊涂了 安静
Hold up, hold up, you fucking me up. Chill out.
你把钱掉地上了
You dropping shit on the ground?
- 等等 - 我没有一天的工夫陪你
- Hold up. - I ain't got all day.
拜托 伙计 这很简单 让我们回过头想想
Come on, man, it's easy. Let's rewind, man.
- 它妈的你在搞什么 - 瞧瞧这玩意儿 哥们
- What the fuck is you doing? - Look at this shit. Look, nigger.
就是刚才在这儿的混蛋
That's the motherfucker right there.
- 谁? - 那个在这儿的白人
- Who? - The white boy right there.
Poot 抓住那个狗娘养的
Poot, grab that motherfucker.
那个白人
The white boy.
- 去叫Dee来 - 等等
- Now got Dee, man - Hold up, man.
拦住那个白鬼!
Stop that white motherfucker.
嘿 混蛋 嘿 兄弟 操
Yeah, motherfucker, yeah, nigger. Fuck that.
你干什么呢 伙计?
What are you doing, man?
冷静 伙计
Calm down, man.
逼我来追 你它妈的搞屁?
Making me run, what the fuck is wrong with you?
- 什么 兄弟 你干嘛追我? - 该死的
- What, man, why you fucking with me? - Shit.
就是这个混蛋使假钱
This the motherfucker right here with the make- believe money.
看到他把钱掉在地上了
Seen his ass drop it and shit.
- 不是我 - 混蛋
- Wasn't me. - Motherfucker.
就是这个混蛋 我看到他了 让这狗娘养的站起来
It was this nigger, I saw him. Get the fuck up.
好了 听着 对不起
All right, listen, I'm sorry.
去它妈的
Fuck that.
我们要做的 这个混蛋骗了我们30美元
What we need to do is, motherfucker burned us for $30.
我们得把这家伙带到Franklin街...
We need to take him to Franklin Ave...
把这混蛋扔到高速路上
and throw his ass right onto the motherfucking expressway.
好了 听着 我它妈的真的很抱歉 我错了 伙计
All right, listen, I'm fucking sorry. I fucked up, man.
- 你身上有什么? - 只有我掉下的10美元 真的一张
- What you got on you? - Just the $10 I dropped, man, the real one.
怎么样啊?
What's up?
该死的
Fuck it.
嘿 就是这样
Hell, yeah.
现在 我们不再归缉毒科管 由Kima梳理案情
For now, we'll work out of Narcotics, with Kima keeping the file.
我们会把所有资料副本 给到法院的Ronnie和你们的人
We'll copy everything to Ronnie at the courthouse and your people.
我们没意见
Fine with us.
McNulty和Santangelo会去查没破的凶杀案
McNulty and Santangelo will work on the open murders...
看有什么能立案上诉的东西
see if anything can be manufactured.
Kima和我的人会在Terrace"钓鱼"
Kima and my people will do hand-to-hand stuff in the Terrace.
诱捕取证 立竿见影
Buy- bust, quick and dirty.
让这些混混吃些官司 我们的麻烦就会少很多
We put years over top of some of these people, we'll roll a few.
你抓不到Avon Barksdale 或者Stringer Bell
You're not gonna get Avon Barksdale or Stringer Bell...
任何高级点 不在街头混的人
or anyone else above the street, not on street rips.
- 你怎么知道 - 这些家伙很厉害
- You don't know that. - These guys are good.
他们根子深 有组织 他们让人闻风丧胆
They're deep and organized. They've got everyone running scared.
你有什么建议?
What do you suggest?
监视小队 电话记录 资产调查
Surveillance teams, DNRs, asset investigation.
利用它们查外围 然后顺藤摸瓜
Keep gathering string till we can find a way in.
不管是电子情报 还是Title III(有线窃听法) 都对这案子有帮助
Either a wired CI or a Title Ill. That's what makes this case.
这就是你对法官说的?
Is that what you told the judge?
好吧 那事上我是个混蛋 但这事上我没有说错
Okay, so I'm an asshole for that. But I'm right about this much.
没有麦克风 没有窃听线 我们要干净 了当
No mics, no wires. We do this fast and clean and simple.
那你干脆别查了
Then you don't do it at all.
在我看来 你们可以在内讧之后 再给检察官办公室打电话
Seems to me you all could've had this fight before calling the State's Attorney's office.
让我问问你
Let me ask you something.
你知道Avon Barksdale什么?
What do we know about Avon Barksdale?
我们知道什么?
What do we know?
这个家伙统治了Franklin Terrace 所有的大楼一年
The guy's owned all of Franklin Terrace for a year.
现在我们有什么他的资料?  一个出生日期 一份犯罪记录?
What do we have on him right now? A DOB? A sheet?
一张身份照片?
A B of I photo?
我们连这个家伙的照片都没有
We don't even have a fucking photo of the guy.
让我喘口气吧 Jimmy
Gimme a break, Jimmy.
两天之前这层楼里谁都不知道这个混混的名字
Two days ago no one on this fucking floor knew this mope's name.
现在他成了个老谋深算的犯罪头子
Now he's some kinda criminal mastermind.
该死的 我说我们就冲到Terrace 大搅一通
Shit, I say we go down to the Terrace and fuck some people up.
你们不需要检察官 你们大妈的需要一个裁判
You all don't need a prosecutor, you need a fucking referee.
等你们知道要怎么查这案子了 吼一声
When you know how you're playing this, give a yell.
我们知道怎么查
We know how we're playing it.
我的人实地去"钓鱼"
My people are going down to do some hand- to- hands.
McNulty和Santangelo探员 会去重查以往的谋杀案记录
Detectives McNulty and Santangelo are going to the hall to review old murder files...
争取新的立案
and try to manufacture a fresh prosecution.
等事情有眉目了  我就去找副局 再要些人手来...
As things heat up, I'll go to the deputy and get us more manpower...
但这案子不能开无轨电车
but this case is not going to sprawl.
从今天起一个月 之后我们各回各的地方
A month from now, we're all gonna be back at our day jobs.
好的
Fine.
给我看你钓的鱼儿们
Bring me your hand-to-hands.
任何有关谋杀案的发现 你可以告诉暴力犯罪科的Llene Nathan
Anything on the murders, you can take to llene Nathan in violent crimes.
我会算上她一个
I'll clue her in.
还有什么事吗?
Anything else?
最后一件
One last thing:
在知会我之前 谁都不能上街行动
No one does anything at all on the street without me knowing about it first.
下级要听上级的 探员
Chain-of-command, Detective.
这是我们这里办案的方法
That's how we do things down this end of the hall.
如果她阻碍你探视 那就告她到法庭呗
If she's fucking you on visitation, take her ass to court.
不是那么简单的 Bunk
Not that simple, Bunk.
法官给了我四个周末里的三个 但仍然需要她配合
Judge gives me three weekends out of four, I still need her to cooperate.
你瞧 调整时间...
You know, move it around...
所以当我不得不工作到周末时 她得和我换时间
so when I have to work through a weekend, she switches with me.
法官给了我三个周末 但没有灵活性
The judge gives me three weekends but no flex...
我还是输
I still lose.
你们没办法协调吗?
You two can't talk this through?
不行
No.
为什么你总是惹得人人恨你呢?
How is it you always got the whole world pissed off at you?
你认识Daniels吗?
You know Daniels?
缉毒科的?
Narcotics?
他怎么了?
What about him?
他负责这个专案组
He's running this detail.
- 那就小心点吧 - 他很狡猾?
- Watch your ass then. - He a snake?
不 他不是那样 但他是坐办公室的
No, he ain't that. But he's a company man.
你瞧 一个有仕途的人
You know, a prospect.
小道消息说下个警区就归他管了
Grapevine says the next district to open up is his.
他在警长的候选名单上?
Shortlist for major?
巴尔的摩市黑人占多数，市长、警局局长职位皆为黑人
他是个黑人 年轻 没有得罪任何人
He's black, he's still young, he hasn't pissed anybody off.
- 该死 他甚至还有个法律学位 - 不会吧
- Shit, he even has a law degree. - No shit.
Baltimore大学 不过还是算的吧
University of Baltimore, but still, you know.
他会搞砸这件Barksdale的案子
He's gonna fuck this Barksdale thing up.
- 怎么会? - 钓鱼执法?
- How's that? - Buy- bust?
他是白费力气 甚至适得其反
He's pissing in the wind.
它早就被你搞砸了 Jimmy
You already fucked it up, Jimmy.
是你惹出来的
You made it happen.
电影“桂河大桥”中主角尼克尔森最后和自己建造的大桥同归于尽
我就像是"桂河大桥"最后那个傻B
I feel like that motherfucker at the end of Bridge On The River Kwai.
我它妈的干了什么啊
What the fuck did I do?
什么桥?
The bridge of what?
你没看过那电影?
You ain't seen that movie?
我倒大霉了
I am fucked.
倒大霉的是我
Fucked is me.
该死的 你这是让我再请你喝一轮
God damn it, you gonna make me go another round.
再来两杯
Two more.
- 做生意就是这样 - 我是说不过就几美元
- It's all in the game. - I'm saying it was only a couple dollars.
- 不是钱的问题 - 但是我们搞得他很惨
- It ain't the money. - But we fucked him up so bad.
这是杀鸡儆猴 Dee
It's the message, Dee.
你不能示弱
You can't show no weakness.
- 不过 我还是要说 - 说什么?
- Still, I'm saying. - What?
String
String.
你都没碰喝的
You ain't touched that drink.
想找个伴吗?
You want some company?
我不是嫖的
I ain't no john.
很好 因为我不是卖的
Good, 'cause I ain't no whore.
我不是什么嫖客 好吗?
I'm not a regular, okay?
- 我为Stringer办事 - 他付你钱 对吧?
- I work for Stringer. - He pay you, don't he?
来吧 请我喝一杯
Come on, buy me a drink.
- 多少? - 20
- How much? - $20.
我喝得慢
I drink slow.
改天吧
Maybe another time.
- 请我一杯吗 亲爱的? - 何不你请我呢?
- Buy me a drink, honey? - How about you buy me a drink?
Carla 这里来一杯
Carla. One here.
- 你在哪儿? - 你觉得呢?
- Where you at? - Where you think?
- 上班晚了? - 一点
- You late for work? - A little.
- 还剩多少? - 姑娘 拜托
- How much you got left? - Girl, please.
10页还有所有的注脚
Ten pages and all the footnotes.
期限?
When's it due?
明天 一上班
Tomorrow, beginning of class.
对你来说 是个漫漫长夜
Long night for you.
漫漫长夜
Long night for me.
我会给你弄点咖啡
I'll make sure and pick up some coffee.
于是 我一路开到Liberty路
So, I drive all the way down to Liberty Road...
在该死的凌晨两点 我还在值夜班
at 2:00 in the damn morning, on a midnight shift...
两起凶杀 一个警察中弹 去干什么呢?
I got two murders and a police shooting going down, to do what?
为了让一只该死的老鼠 滚出我老婆的卧室衣柜
To get a goddamn mouse out of my wife's bedroom closet.
你能想象吗?
Can you imagine that shit?
那你怎么处理的?
So what did you do?
你它妈的以为呢?
What the fuck you think?
我一把老鼠弄出来 就赶回去工作了
I got the mouse out as fast as I could and drove back to work.
还能怎么样
Couldn't do nothing else.
Nadine被这只破老鼠搞疯掉了
Nadine out of her fucking mind over this little - ass field mouse.
她站在椅子上 我就像个该死的卡通人物
She's up on the chair and shit when I come Iike some goddamn cartoon.
我说 你怎么抓住耗子的?
I mean, how'd you catch the mouse?
抓住它? 我烧了它的屁股
Catch him? I lit his ass up.
你开枪打了老鼠?
You shot the mouse?
用你的9mm手枪?(9mm口径)
With your nine?
第一枪打在我老婆的舞鞋上
First shot killed my wife's dress shoe.
第二枪才打中它
Got him with the second.
什么?
What?
你用警枪打了只耗子?
You shot a mouse with your service weapon?
是的
Yeah.
那尸体怎么处理的?
What'd you do with the carcass?
我清理了一下
I cleaned it up, you know.
我考虑过留下那狗娘养的
I thought about leaving that little motherfucker...
来警告剩下的
as a warning to the others.
我操
Fuck me.
现在是早上3:30 我该去交接个早班了
It's 3:30 in the morning. I'm supposed to be early relief.
Jimmy 伙计 我起码得去换套衣服 快点
Jimmy, man, I gotta change my clothes at least, come on.
我要查这案子
I'm gonna do this case.
什么?
What?
我要办这案子 有板有眼的
I'm gonna do this case the way it should be done.
不过是钓鱼执法 Jimmy 速战速决就行了
It's a buy- bust, Jimmy, get in and get out.
- 去它妈的 - Jimmy
- Fuck that. - Jimmy.
今晚到此为止吧
Let's call it a night.
嗨 Bubbs
Hi, Bubbs.
以为你还被关着呢
Thought you was still locked up.
没有
Nope.
你出来多久了?
How long you been home?
三个月了
It's been three months.
你既不留言 也不打电话
You don't write, you don't call.
他是谁
Who's he?
一个朋友
A friend.
他能撑过来吗?
Is he gonna make it?
你还在查毒吗?
You still working drugs?
市里面 是的
Downtown, yeah.
我有料给你
I got something for you.
- 最后一轮 - 操
- Last call. - Fuck.
在Amity小区200号发现尸体
Found body. 200, Block Amity.
我今天有点使不上劲儿 老板
I'm a little thin today, boss.
整个小队都有点弱 记得吗?
The whole squad's a little thin, remember?
自从你的搭档把自己搭进了专案组 我们就少了一个人手
We're down a man since your partner got himself detailed.
是的
Yeah.
我去查
I got it.
老天
Jesus.
- 你好吗 Bobby? - Bunk  你好吗 伙计?
- How you doing, Bobby? - Bunk, what's going on, man?
我们这有人头部中了一 两枪
We got one or two shots to the head.
没有目击者 没有嫌疑犯
No witnesses, no suspects.
在地上有枚.38的弹壳
You got a .380 casing on the ground there.
Buddy 帮我个忙 帮我收起来好吗?
Buddy, do me a favor, bag that for me?
那么 谁报的案?
So, who called it in?
没人 巡警发现的他
No one. 21 Post found him.
人叫William Gant (开头的法庭证人) 42 不 43了
It's a William Gant, 42, no, 43 years old...
家住Schroeder
address on Schroeder.
- 拍过照了吗? - 是的 我们拍了
- You got pictures? - Yeah, we got them.
好了 翻过来吧
Okay, let's roll him.
Gant先生 那个你指认的人
Mr. Gant, do you see the man you identified...
今天在法庭上吗?
sitting in the courtroom today?
他就在那儿
He's right there.
风软FRM字幕组作品 -==http://www.1000fr.net==- 欢迎加入
剧集背景：Baltimore（巴尔的摩市）警局局长直接由市长（Mayor）任命
本剧中所提及的chin-of-command（上下级等级关系）由高到低一般如下：
Commissioner>Deputy of Ops>Major>Lieutenant>Sergeant>Detective/Officer